http://www.law.unlv.edu/website-privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
News CenterCommunications OfficePress Releases & AdvisoriesIn the NewsPublicationsCalendar of EventsSocial MediaStudentsAcademic CalendarCareer Development OfficeExternal ScholarshipsGraduation 2020Journals & Society of AdvocatesLaw School CalendarLearning OutcomesMy BoydLawMy UNLVPublic Interest FellowshipsStudent BlogStudent LifeStudent OrganizationsFaculty & StaffAcademic CalendarLaw School CalendarMy BoydLawStaff DirectoryUNLV Law BlogAlumniAlumni Online DirectoryAlumni of the Year HonoreesBoard of DirectorsBoard Meetings and AgendaEventsGivingPhoto GalleryCommencementTranscript RequestDiploma Reorder ServiceAbout Boyd LawMission & Strategic VisionMeet the DeanAccreditationClass ProfileConsumer Information (ABA Required Disclosures)Statement on NondiscriminationMaps & ParkingContact UsGivingConsumer Information (ABA Required Disclosures)
University of Nevada, Las Vegas
You are hereHome › Website Privacy Policy
Website Privacy Policy
This page was created to inform users of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of our website.
Collection and Use of Information
While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number.
This information will only be used for the purposes for which the form is intended, to respond to the question or comment, and to analyze trends. The message or form may be redirected to another person who is better able to respond to the question or comment. The UNLV William S. Boyd School of Law (BSL) does not market such information. BSL does not use such information in any way that would reveal personally identifying information to outside parties unless we are legally required to do so.
Legal Disclaimer
BSL reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when it believes that disclosure is necessary to protect BSL’s rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" to collect anonymous information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website.
This website uses the following cookies:
Google Analytics: This cookie allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to, page views, source and time spent on the website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals.
Google Adwords: Using Google Adwords we are able to see which pages helped lead to form submissions and clicks. This allows us to make better use of our paid search budget.
Links to Other Websites
This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by BSL. BSL is not responsible for and does not endorse any advertising, products, or resources from such websites. UNLV is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If BSL changes its privacy policy, it will post those changes to this privacy statement so that you are aware of what information BSL collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances it is disclosed. BSL reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review frequently.
AdmissionsJ.D.Apply for J.D.J.D.Tuition & FeesJ.D. Financial AidPublic Interest FellowshipsFAQsApplication RequirementsLL.M.Apply for LL.M.LL.M. Tuition & FeesOnline Information SessionsStudent LifeAbout Boyd LawAcademic ProgramsCareer DevelopmentStudent OrganizationsJournals and Society of AdvocatesVisit UsRecruitment EventsTour & Class VisitMaps & ParkingOfficial ABA DataPreLaw FellowshipAbout Justice DouglasProgram SponsorsSupport the ProgramPreLaw Fellowship ApplicationAcademicsDegree ProgramsJD ProgramsSample Curriculum PlanRequired CoursesElectivesGraduation RequirementsHands-On ExperienceRecruitment EventsDual Degree ProgramsJD/MBAJD/MSWJD/PhDLL.M. In Gaming Law ProgramLL.M. Fast FactsLL.M. AdmissionsLL.M. Tuition & FeesLL.M. CurriculumAsian Study TourLearning OutcomesConcentrationsBusiness and Commercial LawDispute ResolutionHealth LawIntellectual Property LawWorkplace LawAcademic Success Program/CASEFor StudentsExperiential EducationExternshipsCommunity Service ProgramFree Legal EducationPublic Interest FellowshipThomas & Mack Legal ClinicJournals and Society of AdvocatesBook ReviewsNevada Law JournalUNLV Gaming Law JournalSociety of AdvocatesAdvocacy CompetitionsCenters and ProgramsThomas & Mack Legal ClinicKids' Court SchoolThe ProgramResearchOur Founder & DirectorStaffStudent InvolvementLocationsAppointment Request FormOur ClinicsAppellate ClinicEducation Advocacy ClinicFamily Justice ClinicImmigration ClinicOur WorkDeportation DefenseChildren's Rights ProgramUniversity Legal ServicesCommunity EducationStudent ExperienceStaffIn the NewsClinic NewsUseful ResourcesSupport Our WorkContact UsMediation ClinicMisdemeanor ClinicPolicing and Protest ClinicPublic Policy ClinicGet Tax HelpTax Talk TuesdaysFacultyContact UsSaltman Center for Conflict ResolutionAboutAdvisory BoardFacultyStudent FellowsFoundersCurriculumDispute Resolution ConcentrationEventsPast EventsWebcastsPublicationsThe Desert Talking PieceNewsProgramsBusiness and Commercial LawGaming LawHealth Law ProgramIntellectual Property LawInternational LawLawyering Process ProgramRace, Gender & PolicingWorkplace LawFacultyMeet the DeanFull Time FacultyDisability LawAbout the AuthorsRecommended ReadingStatutes and RegulationsJoseph RegaliaProf. Ruben Garcia - PresentationsPublications - Addie C. RolnickPublications - Ann C. McGinleyPublications - Anne TraumPublications - Benjamin EdwardsPublications - Bret C. BirdsongPublications - Daniel W. HamiltonPublications - David OrentlicherPublications - David S. TanenhausPublications - Elizabeth MacDowellPublications - Eric H. FranklinPublications - Eve HananPublications - Francine J. LipmanPublications - Frank CooperPublications - Ian BartrumPublications - Jean SternlightPublications - Jeanne Frazier PricePublications - Jeffrey StempelPublications - Joan HowarthPublications - John Valery WhitePublications - Kathryn M. StanchiPublications - Kay KindredPublications - Keith RowleyPublications - Leslie C. GriffinPublications - Lori D. JohnsonPublications - Lydia NussbaumPublications - Marketa TrimblePublications - Mary Beth BeazleyPublications - Mary LaFrancePublications - Michael KaganPublications - Nancy B. RapoportPublications - Ngai PindellPublications - Rachel J. AndersonPublications - Rebecca NathansonPublications - Rebecca ScharfPublications - Robert I. CorrealesPublications - Ruben J. GarciaPublications - Sara GordonPublications - Stewart ChangPublications - Sylvia LazosPublications - Thomas O. MainVisiting FacultyEmeriti FacultyPublications - Thomas B. McAffeePublications - Christopher L. BlakesleyPublications - Elaine W. ShobenPublications - Linda H. EdwardsPublications - Linda L. BergerPublications - Mary E. BerkheiserPublications - Peter Brandon BayerPublications - Terrill PollmanDistinguished Fellow in Gaming LawDistinguished Fellow in Law and LeadershipDistinguished Fellow in Law and PolicySenior FellowsPublications - Frank FritzPublications - Jay S. BybeeSaltman Senior FellowsAdjunct FacultyPublicationsFaculty in the NewsFaculty EnrichmentCareersFor EmployersFor JudgesFor Current StudentsFor AlumniFor Prospective StudentsReciprocity PolicyBar Exam InformationEmployment StatisticsContact Our OfficeLibraryAbout the Law LibraryLibrary HoursUsing the CollectionLibrary DatabasesForeign Law FinderReservesArticlesBooksFilmsGovernment DocumentsInterlibrary LoansNewspapersResource GuidesFast FactsFaculty and Staff DirectoryContact UsStack GuideFor StudentsFor FacultyFor AlumniFor the PublicLaw Library PoliciesFacility UseComputer Use
Quick access
News CenterCommunications OfficePress Releases & AdvisoriesIn the NewsPublicationsBoyd BriefsUNLV Law MagazineCalendar of EventsSocial MediaStudentsAcademic CalendarCareer Development OfficeExternal ScholarshipsGraduation 2020Journals & Society of AdvocatesLaw School CalendarLearning OutcomesMy BoydLawMy UNLVPublic Interest FellowshipsStudent BlogStudent LifeStudent OrganizationsAmerican Constitution Society for Law and Policy (ACS)Animal Legal Defense Society (ALDS)Asian Pacific American Law Student Association (APALSA)Black Law Students Association (BLSA)Criminal Law Society (CrimLaw)Federalist SocietyGaming Law Society (GLS)Health Law SocietyIntellectual Property Law Society (IPLS)J. Reuben Clark Law Society (JRCLS)La VozLegally SpeakingNevada Justice Association (NJA)OUTLawsOrganization of Part-Time and Non-Traditional Law Students (OPLS)Organization of Women Law Students (OWLS)Phi Alpha Delta (PAD)Public Interest Law AssociationSummer GrantWays to ContributeAnnual Silver State AuctionPast Auction DetailsSociety of Advocates (SOA)Sports and Entertainment Law Association (SELA)Student Bar AssociationGoverning DocumentsMeeting Minutes and AgendasStudent Events CalendarStudents United for Diversity in the Law (SUDL)Boyd Social ClubCannabis Law Society (CLawS)Dispute Resolution SocietyEnvironmental Law Society (ELS)Immigrant Rights Association (IRA)Jewish Law Student Association (JLSA)Legal Association for Space Exploration and Resources (LASER)Middle Eastern Law Students Association (MELSA)Organization of Psychology and Law (OPAL)Policy & Legislative SocietyStudent Mental Health (SMH)Workplace Law ClubData Privacy GroupIf/When/How: Lawyering for Reproductive JusticeNational Lawyers Guild (NLG)Real Estate and Law Society (REALS)Faculty & StaffAcademic CalendarLaw School CalendarMy BoydLawStaff DirectoryUNLV Law BlogAlumniAlumni Online DirectoryAlumni of the Year HonoreesBoard of DirectorsBoard Meetings and AgendaEventsGivingAlumni Leadership CircleAreas to SupportWe Are #BoydNationGiving OptionsAlumni BattlePhoto GalleryCommencementSpring Commencement 2020Spring Commencement 2019Transcript RequestDiploma Reorder ServiceAbout Boyd LawMission & Strategic VisionMeet the DeanAccreditationClass ProfileConsumer Information (ABA Required Disclosures)Statement on NondiscriminationMaps & ParkingContact UsGivingConsumer Information (ABA Required Disclosures)
